

# **Andrés Cecconi**

## **Executive summary**

Creative, team player, enthusiastic and fast learner IT student looking for a career change towards this industry. With over seven years of customer service and supply chain experience in FMCG industry, I am eager to contribute to the company success through hard work.

## Contact



+3492600746



ancecconi15@gmail.com

### **Interests**

- Web development
- Business analysis and process definition
- New technologies
- Information and data management

#### **Technical Skills**

- MS and G Suite
- SQL
- HTML & CSS
- Javascript
- C#
- Visual Studio.

#### Certifications

First Certificate in English University of Cambridge

**SQL Certificate** Educación IT

C# .NET Certificate
Educación IT

Web Development Certificate Educación IT

## Professional career

#### **Inmigrante Gin**

Supply Chain Manager | Feb 2022 - present

- Create the company's supply chain strategy
- Collaborate with other departments to create coordinated plans for business growth
- Communicate and negotiate with suppliers and vendors
- Ensure supply chain processes meet legal requirements and standards

#### Molfino Hnos. S.A.

Supply Chain Specialist | Mar 2020 - Feb 2022

- Maintain adequate inventory and schedule and receive shipments
- Assess current orders and forecast future demand to provide adequate supplies
- Creating reports about supply chain activities such as cost analysis, distribution analysis, feasibility studies, etc.

#### **Boulevard Food Park**

Sr. Customer Service Specialist | Oct 2018 - Mar 2020

- Acts as a liaison between customers and management in order to enhance the overall customer experience
- Monitor customer complaints on social media and reach out to provide assistance
- Assist in training junior Customer Support Representatives
- Jr. Customer Service Specialist | Oct 2015 Mar 2018
- Monitor customer complaints on social media and reach out to provide assistance
- Assist Sr. Customer Service Specialist on problem solving.

# Academic background

Microsoft Solution Developer Web Applications (.NET) Educación IT

**Degree in Administration and Information Management** National University of Rafaela

**Degree in English for Academic Purposes** ISP N°2 "Joaquín V. González"